http://www.seniorlivingexperts.com/privacy-notice/

Privacy Notice
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for seniorlivingexperts.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest. At your option, you may also provide demographic information (such as gender or age) about yourself, but it is not required.
We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.
Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.
We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
We partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the Web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at +773-302-2015 or via email to gabriela@seniorlivingexperts.com.
Schedule a Free Consultation Choose the most convenient time for one of our advisors to give you a call
Addison,Bensenville,60105,60106,60399,Berwyn,60402,Bloomingdale,60108,Bridgeport,62417,Bridgeview,60454,60455,60457,60501,Brookfield,60513,Burr Ridge,60527,Carol Stream,60188,Cicero,60804,Clarendon Hills,60514,Countryside,60525,Darien,60561,Downers Grove,60515,60516,Elmhurst,60106,60126,60181,Forest Park,60130,60546,60682,Glen Ellyn,60137,60138,Glendale Heights,60137,60139,Hillside,60162,Hinsdale,60521,60522,Hodgkins,60525,Indian Head Park,60525,Itasca,60143,La Grange,60525,La Grange Park,60526,Lisle,60532,60563,60572,Lombard,60137,60148,Melrose Park,60160,60161,60163,60164,60165,60171,Naperville,60440,60490,60540,60463,664,North Riverside,60546,Northlake,60164,60165,Oak Brook,60523,Oak Forest,60452,Oak Park,60301,60302,60303,60304,Oakbrook Terrace,60181,River Forest,60153,60160,60305,River Grove,60171,60634,60707,Roselle,Schiller Park,60176,60634,Stickney,60402,Summit,60501,Villa Park,60181,Warrenville,Westchester,60154,Western Springs,60558,Westmont,60523,60559,Wheaton,60187,60189,Willow Springs,60439,60458,60480,60525,60527,Willowbrook,60514,60527,Willowbrook CDP,Winfield,60190,Wood Dale,60191,60399,Woodridge,60439,60440,60516,60517,60565,Aurora,60502,60503,60504,60505,60506,60507,60568,60569,60572,60598,Bartlett,60103,Batavia,60510,Bolingbrook,60440,60446,60490,60517,60565,60585,Burlington,Calumet City,60409,60633,Calumet Park,60827,Campton Hills,60175,Channahon,60410,60450,Chicago Heights,60411,60412,60422,Chicago Ridge,60415,Country Club Hills,60478,Crest Hill,60403,60441,Crestwood,60418,60445,60472,Crete,60417,Dolton,60419,60473,60827,East Hazel Crest,60429,Evergreen Park,60805,Flossmoor,60422,Frankfort,60423,60443,Geneva,60134,Genoa,60135,Hanover Park,60133,60193,Hickory Hills,60457,Homer Glen,60441,60448,60467,60491,Homewood,60430,Lockport,60441,60491,Midlothian,60445,Minooka,60047,Mokena,60448,North Aurora,60542,Oak Lawn,60453,60456,Olympia Fields,60461,Orland Park,60448,60462,60467,60487,Oswego,Palos Heights,60463,60482,Palos Hills,60465,Palos Park,60464,Park Forest,60466,Plainfield,60544,60585,60586,Robbins,60472,Romeoville,60446,Tinley Park,60448,60477,60487,University Park,60417,60449,60466,60484,Wayne,60184,West Chicago,60185,60558,Yorkville,60560,Merrillville,46410,Schererville,46307,46311,46319,46373,46375,Hobart,46342,46410,St John,46373,Dyer,46311 ,Algonquin,60102,Antioch,60002,Barrington,60010,Barrington Hills,60010,Belvidere,61008,Bull Valley,60012,60014,60039,Carpentersville,60110,Cary,60013,Chemung,60033,Cherry Valley,61016,Crystal Lake,60012,60014,60039,Deer Park,60010,East Dundee,60118,Elgin,60120,60121,60122,60123,60124,60140,60170,60175,60177,Forest Lake,60047,Fox Lake,60020,Fox Lake Hills,60046,Fox River Grove,60021,Gages Lake,60030,Gilberts,60136,Grayslake,60030,Greenwood,60097,60098,Hampshire,60140,Harvard,60001,60033,Hawthorn Woods,60047,60060,Hebron,60034,Hoffman Estates,60010,60067,60107,60120,60169,60179,60192,60194,60195,Huntley,60142,Inverness,60010,60067,Johnsburg,60050,60051,Kildeer,60047,60074,Lake Barrington,60010,60084,Lake Bluff,60044,Lake in the Hills,60156,Lake Villa,60046,Lake Zurich,60047,Lakemoor,6003,Lakewood,60050,60051,Lakewood Shores,60481,Lindenhurst,60046,Long Grove,60047,60060,Marengo,60152,McCullom Lake,60050,60051,McHenry,60050,60051,North Barrington,60010,Old Mill Creek,60002,60046,60083,Palatine,60038,60074,60055,60067,60078,60093,Pingree Grove,60140,Port Barrington,60010,Prairie Grove,60012,60014,60039,Richmond,60071,Ringwood,60072,Rockford,61101,61102,61103,61104,61105,61106,61107,61108,61109,61110,61112,61114,61115,61125,61126,Schaumburg,60007,60159,60168,60169,60172,60173,60193,60194,60195,60196,South Barrington,60010,South Elgin,60177,Streamwood,60103,60107,Sugar Grove,60554,Third Lake,60030,Timberlane,Union,60180,Venetian Village,60046,Volo,60020,60030,60041,60051,60073,Wauconda,60084,West Dundee,60118,Wonder Lake,60097,Woodstock,60098,Zion,60099,Arlington Heights,60004,60005,60006,Buffalo Grove,60069,60089,Chicago,Deerfield,60015,Des Plaines,60016,60017,60018,60019,Elk Grove Village,60007,60009,Evanston,60201,60202,60203,60204,60208,60209,Glencoe,60022,Glenview,60016,60025,60026,60029,60062,60082,Golf,60025,60029,Grandwood Park,60031,60046,Green Oaks,60044,60048,Gurnee,60031,60048,Hainesville,60030,60073,Hazel Crest,60429,60430,Highland Park,60035,60040,Highwood,60040,Indian Creek,60061,Kenilworth,60043,Lake Forest,60035,60045,Libertyville,60048,Lincolnshire,60045,60069,Lincolnwood,60645,60712,Mettawa,60045,60048,Morton Grove,60053,Mount Prospect,60005,60056,Mundelein,60048,60060,Niles,60646,60714,North Chicago,60044,60064,60085,60086,60088,Northbrook,60026,60062,60065,Northfield,60093,Park Ridge,60016,60068,Prospect Heights,60004,60062,60070,60090,Riverwoods,60015,Rolling Meadows,60008,60067,60095,Rosemont,60018,Round Lake,60073,Round Lake Beach,60046,60073,Round Lake Heights,60073,Round Lake Park,60030,60073,Skokie,60076,60077,60203,Vernon Hills,60061,60069,Waukegan,60031,60048,60079,60083,60085,60087,Wheeling,60190,Wilmette,60091,Winnetka,60043,60093,,
Sorry but your inquiry falls outside of our coverage zone
I’m inquiring on behalf of myselfI’m inquiring on behalf of my parentI’m inquiring on behalf of my spouseOther
DISCLAIMER: Your privacy is important to us. We don't sell or share any of the information provided to us by our clients. By clicking "Submit" you agree to the terms and conditions of our privacy policy. You also consent that we can reach out to you by phone or email. Your consent is not required to use our service.
Please leave this field empty.
Thank you for your inquiry.
Our advisors will be in touch with you shortly.
What type of care do you need?
Take our short Care Questionnaire to determine which type of care is the best option for your loved one.
Let's get started
I am taking this Care Questionnaire for:
My self
My parent
My spouse
Other
submit
Show variants
Back
Please check all concerns that apply:
Difficulty walking
Memory loss or confusion
Loss of appetite
Mishandled medications
Diminished driving skills
Personality change or moodiness
Loss of interest in hobbies and socializing
Unopened mail or unpaid bills
Difficulty concentrating or poor judgement
Poor housekeeping or unsafe living conditions
If you checked two or more from the list above, you have reason to be concerned and it may warrant an additional conversation with a Senior Living Expert. Call Us at:
1 (773) 938 3772
Back
Next
Does this person need assistance with any of the following?
(Check all that apply or if none, click next)
Getting Dressed
Preparing Meals
Bathing
Taking Medications
Using the Bathroom
Getting to the Doctor's Office
Back
Next
How much professional in-home assistance does this person require?
Less than 2 hours per day
2-5 hours per day
5-12 hours per day
12+ hours per day
Back
Next
Your answers suggest you may need:
Assistance with daily living activities
Robust activity calendar to keep residents busy and engaged
Different levels of care will accommodate residents’ changing needs
Meals, housekeeping, transportation, and utilities included
learn more
Assisted Living
Provides your loved one with assistance in their daily living activities
learn more
Specialized care
Research-based activity calendar specific to those with dementia
Secure, homelike, and comforting environment
Transitional care available for residents’ changing needs
Purposeful features in the environment that support dementia diagnosis
learn more
Memory Care
Specific level of assistance which supports those with Dementia and other types of
Cognitive Impairment.
learn more
Senior Living Communities Benefits
Supports active lifestyles
Great community engagement
Broad variety of amenities
Care services can be purchased on an a la carte basis
learn more
Independent Living
Personal care assistance available for residents with active lifestyles
learn more
Do you need help determining your next steps?
To get in touch with a Senior Living Expert:
Call to further discuss your needs and next steps:
1 (773) 938 3772
Or choose the time that works for you.
request appointment
Compare Cost of Senior Living to Cost of Staying at Home
We've created the "Cost of Senior Living Calculator" to help you compare the cost of senior living with the cost of staying at home.
Let's get started
Before you get started, make sure you have taken our
care questionnaire
to identify the Senior Living option that is right for you.
At-Home Expenses
Expenses
Monthly Cost
1. Mortgage or Rent payment
2. Property tax
3. HOA Fees
4. Utilities/Phone/Internet (total)
5. Lawn Care/Snow Removal
6. Maintenance/Home Repairs
Back
Next
Medical and Daily Life Expenses
Expenses
Monthly Cost
1. In-home Health Care
2. Medical supplies
3. Transportation
4. Social Activities/Hobbies
5. Groceries/Food
Back
Next
What Senior Living options fit my budget?
Please feel free to skip this step if you would rather talk to us directly. Call us at 1 (877) 687 0450
What is your monthly income (Social Security, Investments, Pension)?
< $2,000
$2-5,000
$6-10,000
> $10,000
What assets do you currently own and what is their value?
Back
DISCLAIMER: Your privacy is important to us. We don't sell or share any of the information provided to us by our clients.
Next
Payment/Insurance info
How do you plan on paying for Senior Living?
(Check all that apply or if none, click next)
Private pay
Long term care insurance
VA Benefits
Not sure (don't worry our advisors will be happy to walk you through different options)
Back
Next
Care Type/Living Options
Please select the care type or living option you think is a good fit:
Independent Living
Memory care
Assisted Living
Back
Note: Please use the senior living options suggested by Care Questionnaire or if you'd rather talk to a real person, please call us today at
773-938-3772
Get Result
Based on the information you've provided, below is a cost comparison between senior living and living at home.
0
Your expenses
$0
Cost Range for
INDEPENDENT LIVING in Chicagoland area
We are more than happy to guide you through any financial questions you may have and help you find the right senior living decision for your loved one.
request appointment
Back
